Tilek Zhyrgalbekov

Student

Address Karakol, Issyk-Kul, 722200

Phone 501-341-920

E-mail weekera@gmail.com

A novice IT specialist who is ready to fix faulty equipment, install new assets and maintain continuous business operations, configure computers, servers and peripherals to work within the parameters and security parameters set by the company. Can manage permissions, filters, and file sharing. A novice troubleshooting specialist with an understanding of the architecture and diagnostics of the system. Adapts to rapidly changing work situations and the realities of employees. It is beneficial for all technical operations and technological procedures.

Work History

2019-10 - Video Editing

2019-11 SAPAT Educational Institution, Bishkek

- Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts.

Education

2017-09 - High School Diploma

Current Hussain Karasaev High School - Karakol, 128 Tynystanov Str.

Languages

Russian	
	Very Good
English	
	Good
Kyrgyz	
	Excellent
Turkish	Const
	Good

Skills

Web-based software engineering	
Web Design	
Video Editing	
Data recovery	
Desktop support	
Help Desk Operations	
Computer imaging	
Technical Support	
Hardware and software installation	